<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Basic</string>
    <!--activity_splash-->
    <string name="tvBasic_text">BASIC PROJECT</string>
    <!--activity_term_of_use-->
    <string name="alert_should_check">You should check Term of Use before enter Main screen</string>
    <string name="title_term">
        <u>Term of Use</u>
    </string>
    <!--activity_main-->
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <!--dialog_term-->
    <string name="tvAgree_text">Agree</string>
    <string name="term_of_user">In user-centered design, personas are created to represent the types of users.
        It is sometimes specified for each persona\n which types of user interfaces it is comfortable with
        (due to previous experience or the interface\'s inherent simplicity),
        and what technical expertise and degree of\n knowledge it has in specific fields or disciplines.
        When few constraints are imposed on the end-user\n category, especially when designing programs for use
        by the general public, it is common practice to \nexpect minimal technical expertise or previous training in end
        users.\n
        Originally used in reference to human-computer interactions - and still largely associated with those
        disciplines -
        the term is now used to refer to any specific human-design interaction, ranging from a digital device, to a
        sales process,
        to an entire conference. Perhaps due to its organic development and lack of formalization, "User Experience" may
        be
        defined by, and the responsibility of, very different departments from organization to organization: in some
        organizations, it is owned by marketing; in others, it falls under information technology (IT). Then, from a
        solutions perspective, some organizations base their "User Experiences" around the research and academic-based
        approaches of human-computer interaction (HCI); others treat interface and/or product design as the source for
        "User Experience," while still others let marketing or IT drive it.
    </string>

    <string name="title_followers">Followers</string>
    <string name="messenge_no_internet">No Internet</string>
</resources>
